Guide to the Vincent Price Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographs, 1890s-1980s; Series VII
  - Oversize
    - Other individuals
      - Browne, Coral (Box 18, Folder 215)
        See also: Folder 198
      - Price family (Box 18, Folder 216)
        See also: Folder 199
      - Miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 217)
- Additional material, Accession 2004-M-017; 0.25
  - "Vincent Price at Yale", 1986 spring
    Student film interview of Vincent Price discussing his days at Yale, film roles, the place of film study at Yale, concluding with a fundraising appeal to alumni to establish a tenured position in film studies.
    - Original, 1 (Box 1)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Original audiotape, videotape, and motion picture films, as well as preservation masters and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers needing to consult the original materials should refer to the finding aid and/or a reference archivist to determine policies governing reproduction for access.
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 1U)